Thinking XXX is a documentary film directed by Timothy Greenfield-Sanders.
For a book project, photographer Timothy Greenfield-Sanders took photographs of 30 stars of
adult movies, each pair of photographs in the same pose, clothed and nude.
This film records the photo shoots and includes interviews with the
performers and commentary from eight writers (and John Waters).
The actors and writers discuss economics, nudity and
exhibitionism, careers, and private lives.
Self, played by Jenna Jameson.
Self, played by Ron Jeremy.
Self, played by Tera Patrick.
Self, played by Belladonna.
Self, played by Sunrise Adams.
Self, played by Briana Banks.
Thinking XXX is a 2004 documentary television film about the process photographer Timothy
Greenfield-Sanders went through to create his book XXX: 30 Porn Star Portraits.
The film explores themes of pornography, interview, photo shoot, voyeur.